JOSEPH E. PERSICO PAPERS (APAP030) 1910-2003
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
1970 August 3 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Department of Environmental Conservation Pesticides Hearing
1970 August 4 Queens, NY, Meeting on Drug Abuse
1970 August 4 Queens, NY, Excerpts, at Airport before meeting on Drug Abuse
1970 August 4 Long Island, NY, TV Interview, following meeting on Drug Abuse
1970 August 4 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Williamsburg Center for the Retarded
1970 August 6 Buffalo, NY, Address, International Typographical Convention
1970 August 6 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, International Typographical Convention
1970 August 6 Rochester, NY, Address, New York State Construction Trades Council Convention
1970 August 6 Rochester, NY, Excerpts, New York State Construction Trades Council Convention
1970 August 6 Buffalo, NY, Joint Press Conference, at Staten Hilton Hotel
1970 August 7 Saratoga, NY, Excerpts, Saratoga Performing Arts Center
1970 August 9 Ozarks, MO, News Conference, National Governors Conference
1970 August 10 New York City, NY, Ceremony appointing Betty Furnes
1970 August 10 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Ceremony appointing Betty Furnes
1970 August 10 New York City, NY, Radio Interview, Station WNEW
1970 August 10 New York City, NY, Interview, with Joe Alvarze NBC
1970 August 11 Ozarks, MO, Excerpts, Meeting of National Governors Conference
1970 August 12 Amherst, NY, Excerpts, Meeting on Drug Abuse, Sweet Home High School
1970 August 12 Rochester, NY, Excerpts, Pulaski Park Concert
1970 August 12 Rochester, NY, Excerpts, Brown Square Playground
1970 August 13 Rochester, NY, Television Interview, with Eddie Meath WHEC-TV
1970 August 13 Rochester, NY, Monroe County Environmental Forum
1970 August 13 Seneca Falls, NY, Excerpt, 50th Anniversary of Suffrage
1970 August 14 New York City, NY, Radio Interview, with Jim Gash
1970 August 14 New York City, NY, Interview, with Jackie Hayward WCBS
1970 August 14 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Drug Out Day Parade
1970 August 14 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Associates of the Rockefeller Team
1970 August 18 Queens, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Children's Psychiatric Center
1970 August 19 Liverpool, NY, Onondaga County Environmental Forum
1970 August 19 Watertown, NY, Excerpts, 98th Annual Convention of Firemen's Association
1970 August 20 Waverly, NY, Excerpts, Joint Service Clubs Luncheon
1970 August 25 Deerfield, NY, TV Taping, WKTV
1970 August 25 Ticonderoga, NY, Excerpts, 150th Anniversary Celebration
1970 August 25 Malone, NY, Excerpts, Joint Services Club Luncheon
1970 August 26 Cortland, NY, Excerpts, Joint Services Club Luncheon
1970 August 27 New York City, NY, TV Interview, with Ralph Penga
1970 August 27 New York City, NY, Excerpts, AMVETS 26th National Convention
1970 August 27 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Salutes Miss Universe Convention
1970 August 28 Albany, NY, Press Release, Use of discriminatory language describing organized crime Italian Americans
1970 September 2 New York City, NY, Television Interview, Endorsement by Patrolmen's Association
1970 September 2 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Chamber of Commerce Annual Farm Dinner
1970 September 3 New York City, NY, Interview, Zionist Organization of America
1970 September 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Zionist Organization of America
1970 September 6 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Jewish Teachers Association Awards Presentation
1970 September 8 New York City, NY, Interview, Additional Funding for Narcotics Control
1970 September 8 New York City, NY,, Additional Funding for Narcotics Control
1970 September 8 Hempstead, LI, Remarks, Rockefeller at CASO Headquarters
1970 September 9 Rochester, NY, TV Interview, at Monroe County Airport
1970 September 9 Irondequoit, NY, Governor's Meeting on Drug Abuse
1970 September 9 Irondequoit, NY, Excerpts, Governor's Meeting on Drug Abuse
1970 September 9 Hornell, NY, Remarks, Chamber of Commerce
1970 September 9 Hornell, NY, Excerpts, Chamber of Commerce
1970 September 10 Albany, NY, Press Conference, Council of the Arts
1970 September 10 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Council of the Arts
1970 September 10 Albany, NY, Remarks, Fred Field Headquarters
1970 September 10 Albany, NY, TV Interview, Fred Field WROW
1970 September 10 Albany, NY, News Conference, Rockefeller and Albany Rotary Club
1970 September 10 Albany, NY, Remarks, Meeting on Children and Youth
1970 September 10 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Meeting on Children and Youth
1970 September 10 Albany, NY, Remarks, Dedication of New Wing of New York State Civil Service Building
1970 September 10 Yonkers, NY, Remarks, Yonkers Republican Committee
1970 September 11 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Rockefeller and F.W.H Adams
1970 September 11 Brooklyn, NY, Remarks, Plaque to Rockefeller at Yeshiva Toras Emes
1970 September 11 Brooklyn, NY, Remarks, Mesifta Baes Schmuel
1970 September 12 Washington, D.C., Conference on Drug Abuse
1970 September 12 Washington, D.C., Press Conference, Following Conference on Drug Abuse
1970 September 14 New York City, NY, Mario Procaccino's Endorsement of Rockefeller
1970 September 14 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Publishers Association Luncheon
1970 September 14 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Publishers Association Luncheon
1970 September 14 Albany, NY, News Interview, after New York State Publishers Association Luncheon
1970 September 15 Scarsdale, NY, Remarks, Advertising Club of Westchester
1970 September 15 New York City, NY, Remarks, 100 Black Men Dinner
1970 September 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 100 Black Men Dinner
1970 September 15 Saratoga, NY, Excerpts, Inauguration of Ewald B. Wyguist
1970 September 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Garment Center Congregation
1970 September 16 Brooklyn, NY, Remarks, Hostel for Retarded Young Adults
1970 September 16 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Hostel for Retarded Young Adults
1970 September 16 Garden City, NY, Excerpts, Governor's Meeting on Drug Abuse
1970 September 16 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Port of Albany Dinner
1970 September 17 Liverpool, NY, Excerpts, Governor's Meeting on Drug Abuse
1970 September 17 Lake Placid, NY, Excerpts, Associated Industries of New York State Dinner
1970 September 18 Scarsdale, NY, Excerpts, Advertising Club of Westchester Luncheon
1970 September 19 New York City, NY, Endorsement of Rockefeller by Paul Screvane
1970 September 22 Batavia, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Rt. 63 South
1970 September 22 Albion, NY, Remarks, Orleans County Republican Committee
1970 September 22 Cambia, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking of Niagara Community College
1970 September 23 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Touchdown Club Luncheon
1970 September 23 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Older American White House Forum
1970 September 24 Garden City, NY, News Interview, at Garden City Hotel
1970 September 24 Garden City, NY, Excerpts, Long Island Press Annual Distinguished Service Award Dinner
1970 September 24 New York City, NY, Endorsement of Rockefeller by Uniform Sanitation
1970 September 25 Poughkeepsie, NY, Excerpts, Arlington Sewer Treatment Facilities Dedication
1970 September 25 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Puerto Rican Homeowners Association
1970 September 25 Great Neck, NY, Excerpts, Sanctuary and New School of Temple Beth-El
1970 September 25 Monticello, NY, Excerpts, 37th Annual Convention of New York State Conservation Council
1970 September 28 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Associated Press Luncheon
1970 September 28 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Associated Press Luncheon
1970 September 28 Albany, NY, Q and A Session
1970 September 30 New York City, NY, Remarks, West Farm Housing Development
1970 October 2 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Republican Committee Annual All Star Gala
1970 October 2 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Urban Development and Corporation
1970 October 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Office and Professional Employees Local 153
1970 October 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, "Man of the Year Award" Dinner Dance
1970 October 4 Garden City, LI, Remarks, Nassau Press Association
1970 October 4 Matinecock, LI, Excerpts, Women's Rally for Rockefeller
1970 October 6 Hamburg, NY, Erie County Environmental Forum
1970 October 6 Hamburg, NY, Excerpts, Erie County Environmental Forum
1970 October 6 Kenmore, NY, Excerpts, Great Lakes Commission Awards Presentation
1970 October 6 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, Great Lakes Commission Awards Presentation
1970 October 7 New York City, NY, Press Interview, New York Daily News
1970 October 7 Staten Island, NY, Remarks, Richmond County Republican Committee
1970 October 7 Staten Island, NY, Excerpts, Richmond County Republican Committee
1970 October 7 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Brooklyn Headquarters Opening
1970 October 8 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Rockefeller and Honorable Abba Eban
1970 October 8 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Rockefeller Endorsement by Pamos
1970 October 8 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Local 144 Service Employees International Union
1970 October 9 New York City, NY, News Conference, Wins Panel Program
1970 October 9 New York City, NY, Announcement, Ed Cavanaugh
1970 October 9 New York City, NY, Excerpts, War Against Drug Addiction
1970 October 12 New York City, NY, Announcement, Judge S.J. Riebowitz
1970 October 12 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Columbus Citizens Committee
1970 October 12 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Visit to 7th Street and Avenue D
1970 October 13 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Senior Citizens
1970 October 13 Huntington, NY, Excerpts, Long Island Railroad Electrification Ceremony
1970 October 13 Hauppauge, NY, Excerpts, Construction Start of State Office Building
1970 October 13 Baldwin, NY, Excerpts, Nassau County Village Officials Annual Dinner
1970 October 14 Newburg, NY, Interview, Q and A Session
1970 October 14 Newburg, NY, Press Conference, Newburg and Middleton Editors
1970 October 14 Albany, NY, Remarks, South Mall Towers, Construction Start
1970 October 14 Albany, NY, Excerpts, South Mall Towers, Construction Start
1970 October 14 Albany, NY, Remarks, Al Smith Exhibit
1970 October 14 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Al Smith Exhibit
1970 October 15 New York City, NY, Television Taping, with Mike Wallace
1970 October 15 New York City, NY, Press Interview, with Marth Deanne WOR
1970 October 15 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Q and A Session
1970 October 15 New York City, NY, Mesting and Uniformed Sanitation Workers
1970 October 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Mesting and Uniformed Sanitation
1970 October 15 Lake Success, NY, Excerpts, Cornerstone Laying Medical Society of New York State
1970 October 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Nationalities Dinner
1970 October 16 New York City, NY, Remarks, Columbus Citizens Committee
1970 October 16 New York City, NY, Remarks, MTA Stewart Airport
1970 October 16 New York City, NY, Revised Excerpts, MTA Stewart Airport
1970 October 16 New York City, NY, Remarks, Service Employees
1970 October 16 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Polish American Democratic Committee
1970 October 16 New York City, NY, Remarks, Mayors from Italy
1970 October 16 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Hispanic Transit Society Inc.
1970 October 17 Queens, NY, Remarks, Federation of Civic Council Annual Convention
1970 October 17 Lido Beach, NY, Remarks, Long Island Columbia Association 15th Italian Americans Achievement Award Dinner
1970 October 17 Lido Beach, LI, Excerpts, 15th Achievement Award Dinner
1970 October 17 Queens, NY, Excerpts, Federation of Civic Councils
1970 October 18 New York City, NY, Remarks, Shomrim Society
1970 October 18 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Shomrim Society
1970 October 18 New York City, NY, TV Interview, Searchlight NBC Studies
1970 October 18 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Electrical Welfare Club
1970 October 18 Bronx, NY, Excerpts, Cadet Headquarters Groundbreaking
1970 October 19 Queens, NY, Remarks, Democrats for Rockefeller
1970 October 19 Queens, NY, Press Interview, Democrats for Rockefeller
1970 October 19 Rochester, NY, Press Interview, on arrival at Airport
1970 October 19 Rochester, NY, Remarks, New York State Narcotic Control Commission Conference
1970 October 19 Rochester, NY, Excerpts, New York State Narcotic Control Commission Conference
1970 October 19 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Lindsay's Endorsement of Goldberg
1970 October 20 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Women for Rockefeller
1970 October 20 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Women for Rockefeller
1970 October 20 New York City, NY, Rally for Republican Candidate
1970 October 21 New York City, NY, Remarks, Honorary Degree to Rockefeller Pace College
1970 October 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Honorary Degree to Rockefeller Pace College
1970 October 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Alfred and Smith Memorial Foundation
1970 October 22 Bohemia, NY, Remarks, Building and Construction Trade Council
1970 October 22 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Meeting with El Diario Editores
1970 October 22 White Plains, NY, Remarks, General Foods Corporation
1970 October 22 New York City, NY, Remarks, Gabe Pressman's Journalism Class
1970 October 22 New York City, NY, Remarks, St. John's University
1970 October 22 New York City, NY, Press Interview, St. John's University
1970 October 23 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Community Leaders Endorsement of Rockefeller
1970 October 23 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Grant Award to New York State Public Library Research
1970 October 25 Pocantico Hills, NY, Excerpts, Weeklies for Rockefeller Reception
1970 October 26 New York City, NY, Remarks, Mayors of Puerto Rico
1970 October 26 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Jater Faith Association
1970 October 27 Buffalo, NY, Press Interview, Jack Kemp Testimonial
1970 October 27 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, Jack Kemp Testimonial
1970 October 27 Long Island, NY, Excerpts, Long Island Rail Road Strike
1970 October 27 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Contract Signing between Penn Central and MTA
1970 October 28 New York City, NY, TV Debate, Rockefeller with A. Goldberg, P. Adams *1964 Campaign
1970 October 29 New York City, NY, Endorsement of Rockefeller by Orthodox Rabbis
1970 October 29 Queens, NY, TV Interview, WPIX on Walking Tour
1970 October 29 New York City, NY, News Conference, Eyewitness News WABC
1970 October 30 Rochester, NY, TV Taping, Rockefeller on WOKR
1970 October 30 Rochester, NY, Remarks, Rockefeller at Seneca Towers
1970 November 1 New York City, NY, TV Debate, Rockefeller with A. Goldberg, P. Adams
1970 November 3 New York City, NY, Acceptance Speech for 4th Term
1970 November 18 Washington, D.C., News Conference, Rockefeller at White House
1970 November 18 Queens, NY, TV Interview, with Jerry Wilson WCBS
1970 November 20 New York City, NY, Remarks, Building Industry Employers Association
1970 November 20 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Building Industry Employers Association
1970 November 30 New York City, NY, New York County Executive Association
1970 November 30 New York City, NY, News Conference, New York County Executive Association
1970 December 1 San Juan, PR, Address, National Association of State Legislatures
1970 December 1 San Juan, PR, Address, National Association of State Legislatures
1970 December 1 New York City, NY, Remarks, 100th Anniversary of the YWCA
1970 December 1 New York City, NY, Remarks, 90th Annual New York Board of Rabbis
1970 December 1 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 90th Annual New York Board of Rabbis
1970 December 10 New York City, NY, Joint Press Conference, Board of Urban Affairs
1970 December 10 New York City, NY, Press Interview, New York City Minority Employment
1970 December 10 New York City, NY, Remarks, Legislative Committee on Housing and Urban Development
1970 December 10 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Legislative Committee on Housing and Urban Development
1970 December 10 Colonie, NY, Testimonial for Ed M. Galvin
1970 December 11 Hauppauge, LI, Suffolk Town Meeting
1970 December 16 Albany, NY, News Conference, "Big Six" Mayors
1970 December 16 Albany, NY, Press Conference, Republican County Leaders
1970 December 17 New York City, NY, Remarks, State Traffic Safety Council
1970 December 17 New York City, NY, Excerpts, State Traffic Safety Council
1970 December 17 New York City, NY, Remarks, Maccabean Festival
1970 December 17 New York City, NY, News Interview, Reception for Senator Goodell
1970 December 20 Albany, NY, Discussion with Firefighters
1970 December 21 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Dunn Memorial Bridge Opening
1970 December 29 Albany, NY, Off the-record interview, with LCA reporters
1970 December 30 New York City, NY, TV Interview, Rockefeller with Jerome Wilson
1970 December 30 New York City, NY, Interview, with Pail Hoffman
1970 December 31 New York City, NY, Swearing in of Rockefeller
1970 December 31 New York City, NY, News Conference, Swearing in of Rockefeller
1971
1971 January 1 Albany, NY, Address, Inaugural Address of Rockefeller
1971 January 1 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Inaugural Address of Rockefeller
1971 January 3 Washington, D.C., TV Interview, Meet the Press, NBC
1971 January 5 Albany, NY, Remarks, Republican Assembly Members
1971 January 6 Albany, NY, Address, State of the State Address
1971 January 14 New York City, NY, Interview, with Radio Correspondents
1971 January 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, Federation of Jewish Philanthropies
1971 January 14 New York City, NY, TV Interview, Ralph Penza and Gave Pressman
1971 January 15 Niagara, NY, Remarks, Tribute to Mayor E. Dent Lackey
1971 January 15 Niagara, NY, Excerpts, Tribute to Mayor E. Dent Lackey
1971 January 15 Niagara, NY, TV Interview, Before Tribute to Mayor Lackey
1971 January 16 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Anniversary Dinner at Young Israel Synagogue
1971 January 18 New York City, NY, Remarks, Governor's Club Dinner
1971 January 20 New York City, NY, Address, The Economic Club of New York
1971 January 20 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Telegram to New York Congressional Delegation
1971 January 20 Albany, NY, Statement, Federal Revenue Sharing
1971 January 26 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Association for Mental Health
1971 January 26 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Association for Mental Health
1971 January 26 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Conference of Mayors
1971 January 26 Albany, NY, Press Interview, Regarding Budget
1971 January 28 New York City, NY, Remarks, Westchester County Republican Committee
1971 January 29 New York City, NY, Interview, with Jerry Wilson of WCBS- TV
1971 January 29 Washington, D.C., Statement to, the Joint Economic Committee of Congress
1971 January 29 New York City, NY, Remarks, Federation of Women's Republican Club
1971 February 5 White Plains, NY, Excerpts, United Fund of Westchester Dinner
1971 February 9 New York City, NY, Interview, following taping of Governor's Report
1971 February 9 New York City, NY, Remarks, Association of Towns
1971 February 9 Albany, NY, Address, to Executive Chamber of Commerce
1971 February 9 Albany, NY, Excerpts, to Executive Chamber of Commerce
1971 February 9 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Association of the Fire District Meeting
1971 February 16 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Publishers Association
1971 February 16 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Publishers Association
1971 February 21 Warrenton, VA, Remarks, National Urban Coalition Conference
1971 February 22 Albany, NY, Address, New York State Committee for Children: Department of Mental Hygiene
1971 February 22 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Committee for Children: Department of Mental Hygiene
1971 February 22 Albany, NY, Excerpts and Statement, Revenue Sharing Day
1971 February 24 Washington, D.C., Press Interview, New Senate Office Building
1971 February 24 Washington, D.C., Response of Session
1971 March 1 Albany, NY, Address, New York State AFL-CIO
1971 March 1 Albany, NY, Address, New York State Council of Churches, Red Room
1971 March 1 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Council of Churches, Red Room
1971 March 1 Albany, NY, Address, New York State Council of Churches, United Methodist Trinity Church
1971 March 1 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Council of Churches, United Methodist Trinity Church
1971 March 2 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Press Conference regarding New York City Schools
1971 March 3 Albany, NY, Press Conference, Politics, Goodell, Livett
1971 March 9 Albany, NY, Remarks, Citation to Ed Mason
1971 March 9 Albany, NY, Remarks, League of Women Voters
1971 March 9 Albany, NY, Excerpts, League of Women Voters
1971 March 9 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Broadcasters Association
1971 March 13 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Federation of Republican Clubs
1971 March 18 New York City, NY, Remarks, United Jewish Appeal of New York
1971 March 18 New York City, NY, Excerpts, United Jewish Appeal of New York
1971 March 21 New York City, NY, Radio Interview, Albert Einstein Medical College Founders Dinner
1971 March 21 New York City, NY, Remarks, Albert Einstein Medical College Founders Dinner
1971 March 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Albert Einstein Medical College Founders Dinner
1971 March 30 Albany, NY, Remarks, Meeting of Republican County Leaders
1971 March 30 Albany, NY, Press Interview, following Meeting of Republican County Leaders
1971 April 5 Albany, NY, Remarks, The Presidents Club
1971 April 6 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Inauguration of Ernest Boyer as SUNY Chancellor
1971 April 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, Harvard Club
1971 April 15 New York City, NY, Remarks, Northeastern Chairman's Association
1971 April 15 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Prior to Social Services Steering Committee
1971 April 15 New York City, NY, Remarks, Social Services Steering Committee
1971 April 15 New York City, NY, Press Interview, following Social Services Steering Committee
1971 April 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Social Services Steering Committee
1971 April 16 Bronx, News Interview, Dedication of Harlem River Park
1971 April 16 Bronx, Remarks, Dedication of Harlem River Park
1971 April 16 Bronx, Excerpts, Dedication of Harlem River Park
1971 April 19 New York City, Remarks, Associated Press Annual Meeting
1971 April 19 New York City, News Interview, following Associated Press Annual Meeting
1971 April 19 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, Building and Construction Trades Legislative Conference
1971 April 23 New York City, NY, Remarks, Congressional Medal of Honor Awards
1971 April 23 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Congressional Medal of Honor Awards
1971 April 26 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Prior to AMA Conference on Environmental Health
1971 April 26 New York City, NY, Remarks, AMA Conference on Environmental Health
1971 April 26 New York City, NY, Excerpts, following AMA Conference on Environmental Health
1971 April 26 New York City, NY, Remarks, AME Zion Church Conference
1971 April 27 Albany, NY, Press Conference, US Conference of the World Council of Churches
1971 April 27 Albany, NY, Remarks, US Conference of the World Council of Churches
1971 April 27 Albany, NY, Excerpts, US Conference of the World Council of Churches
1971 April 27 Albany, NY, Rockefeller and New York City Labor Leaders
1971 April 28 Albany, NY, Rockefeller and Puerto Rican Coordinating Committee
1971 May 2 New York City, NY, Remarks, St. George Association Annual Communion Breakfast
1971 May 2 New York City, NY, Excerpts, St. George Association Annual Communion Breakfast
1971 May 4 New York City, NY, Remarks, International Symposium on Public Employees Labor Relations
1971 May 6 Long Island, NY, Remarks, Queens County Republican Committee
1971 May 7 New York City, NY, Remarks, Governor's Conference on Aging
1971 May 7 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Governor's Conference on Aging
1971 May 11 Rochester, NY, Remarks, Dedication at Eastman Kodak
1971 May 11 Rochester, NY, Excerpts, Dedication at Eastman Kodak
1971 May 11 Rochester, NY, Media Interview, at Monroe Airport
1971 May 13 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Brazilian American Chamber of Commerce Dinner